# Md Shadman Tajwar Haque

68 Corporate Drive, Scarborough, ON, M1H 3H3 (647) 510 6867 tajwar@ieee.org tajwar.ml linkedin.com/in/tajwarhaque

## Summary

A Masters of Engineering in Electrical and Computer Engineering graduate candidate with technical work experience in the Telecommunications and Health Care Industry. An active member of IEEE since 2016, while volunteering under several organizations across the Asia Pacific region under several roles.

#### **Education**

University of Windsor, ON, Canada Masters of Engineering – Electrical and Computer Engineering June, 2020 – August, 2021

American International University – Bangladesh (AIUB), Dhaka, Bangladesh
Bachelor of Science – Electrical and Electronics
Engineering
August, 2014 – February, 2018

## **Publication**

Design and Implementation of an IoT based Automated Agricultural Monitoring and Control System – 2019 International Conference on Robotics, Electrical and Signal Processing Techniques (ICREST) [Published: February 21, 2019]

Link: ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/8644212

#### **Skills**

- Python (NumPy, Matplotlib, Pandas, Seaborn)
- Machine Learning (Scikit Learn, Tensorflow, Keras)
- MATLAB
- Tableau
- SQL
- Excel

# Experience

Programmer, C and T Home Care Limited, New York, NY, USA

January, 2020 - June, 2020

Developed the company website, worked on CRM and prepared documents.

*Skills Used:* Web Design (HTML, CSS and JS), Adobe Suite (Illustrator, Photoshop, XD and After Effects) and QuickBase.

Company Webiste: candthomecare.com

Service Assurance and Experience Technology Intern, Banglalink Digital Communications Limited, Dhaka, Bangladesh

May, 2018 - August, 2018

Analyzed and prepared reports on daily user complaints and numerous quality assurance data.

Skills Used: Microsft and Adobe Suite. Company Website: banglalink.net

# **Projects**

Link to Projects: <u>projects.tajwar.ml</u>

### **Interests**

- Machine Learning
- Computer Vision
- Data Science
- Analytics